https://www.numericalinnovations.com/pages/privacy-policy

Software products
Numerical cloudFab 3000Ace 3000EasygerbDfm now!Oem / custom software
Support
Find activation codeHelp centerSubmit a ticketLifetime maintenanceDxf conversion guidelinesPostscript and pdf guidelinesNumerical matrix file descriptionCam library - api documentation
Order nowAbout usBlog
Shopping cart
close
No products in the cart.
FacebookTwitterInstagramYouTube
Blog
Request quote
Contact us
Log in
The Numerical Innovations, Inc. Privacy Policy describes how we treat your information when you visit our website and use our software tools.
Website Privacy Policy:
We respect your privacy and do not collect any cookies, log files, or anything else related during your visit on this website.
Users might be asked to fill out a web form by providing name and email address to receive more information, technical assistance, download links to our software products, etc. We use secure e-mail systems provided by ( aweber & wufoo ) and we reserve the right to contact users with information related to this website and/or our software products. User information is never shared with 3rd parties, and users may unsubscribe anytime or contact us directly to be removed from our e-mail list.
Software Privacy Policy:
No personal information or information about end users or their computer configuration is transferred other than the following:
There is a one-way hash of some machine configuration data sent to the license server - however no personal information will be transferred.
One-way Hash: Codes that identify parts of the computer are put through a special function (called a 'one way hash') that turns the codes into one code number that is unique to the end user’s computer but cannot be deciphered (or reverse engineered) to determine what those components are. Only this hash value is sent to the activation server and not the details on the computer parts.
If the user has purchased software, they will receive an "Activation Code". During registration they will be required to enter a unique activation password and their e-mail address. This allows the user to receive (via e-mail) their license information again should they loose their activation code, forget the password, etc.
Note: We also offer optional FLEXnet license keys which do not require activation.
This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email.
Scroll To TopScroll To Top
